Man. I thought you
missed the train.
Good evening Phil.
I thought so too.
- Did you at least sleep a little?
- Yes.
Well. a little bit.
Did you pick something up?
- No. definitely not. Phil?
- But you are on it.
No. I'm not. Phil.
Michael...
Michael would like to ask you
a few questions personally.
He is also on the train.
- You know that...
- Yes. I know. that's not your thing...
-... but the publicity....
- Can not you do that for me?
- You know it does not work that way.
- You know the answers.
He wants you. Oliver.
- So?
- Yes. okay...
- Thanks. Oliver.
- Clear.
I feel like your movie...
... was inspired by a
kind of childhood memory.
From my childhood?
- No. I had a normal childhood.
- A normal? In Spain?
Hard to believe.
No. I grew up outside. very
close to. um. Washington D.C.
In the suburb. Yes.
We first moved to Spain when I was 12.
Do you have an explanation for the basic
topic "Search" in your new movie?
For sure.
My main actor...
loses his innocence.
Then he realizes that everything else
that seemed easy is now quite complex.
Much harder than he would like.
And he sets out on a journey
to regain his innocence.
- What is impossible. as you know.
- Hi.
- I was looking for you.
- Oh. hi. Karen.
Hi.
Sit down. if you like.
I am giving an interview.
Let's move on?
Sit down please.
- Yes. only to. yes. Continue.
- So. Oliver...
What your movie character then finds is...
Scary.
Uh. terrible.
What makes you hope your
character regains his innocence?
This is what the film is
about. that it does not work.
So that fear sneaks
into our lives...
... or we allow feelings like
fear. jealousy and fear...
... things that make
it impossible to...
- Are you doing well?
- Yes sorry.
OK.
- Hi. My name is Karen.
- Michael.
Hi. Nice to meet you. Michael.
And where does the article appear...
Michael?
Sweetie. why do not you
go back to our place.
We still need about an hour.
Trying to sober up. okay?
- You're an asshole. right?
- Okay...
- Okay.
- Thanks a lot for this.
- Yes. I am leaving.
- Okay.
But first...
Do you give me the bottles?
- Which bottles?
- The bottles.
The you have taken
from the minibar.
I do not have any bottles.
What do you mean. you have none?
You took her out of the minibar.
- No idea what you want. Hey! Hey!
- What does this mean?
What's that about?
I do not have any bottles. babe. OK?
- I do not know where they are.
- I do not believe you!
- Did you throw her away?
- No. I do not know where they are. okay?
Now lie down please.
Shit.
Wow. the lady is angry.
Is this your girlfriend?
- Would you like us to continue?
- Yes. please.
We spoke of...
Innocence.
Oliver. do you remember
when you lost yours?
- That's a good question.
- Thank you.
You can hardly fix this
on a single point. right?
No.
It happens over a period of time.
And it's kind of abstract too.
Well...
There is already something that comes to my mind.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes. Do tell.
I was 14 or 15 at the time.
And I lived with my dad and his
wife in Spain at the time.
We lived in this
house with garden.
And I remember standing on
the balcony in the evening.
I just stood there
staring at the moon.
It was a beautiful summer night.
And then I heard a splash.
I looked down and there was the
dog that my father had bought...
... for my little sister.
It was a puppy. at most 4. 5 days old.
Anyway. he managed to
sneak out of the house...
... over to the pool.
and fell into it.
I was mesmerized by the survival
instinct of this little guy.
He paddled as if obsessed
not to go under.
Anyway. I went down to
fish him out of the water.
But when I arrived. the kid had
made it to the middle of the pool.
And he fidgeted and whined a lot. in
his desperate attempt to survive.
Then he did not move anymore.
I remember how shocked I was...
... because I was so sure
that he would do it.
That his instinct keeps him
alive until I am with him.
But instinct is not enough.
He made the wrong decision and drowned.
And that shocked me.
- And then...
- He drowned? Or did you let him drown?
No. he drowned.
Yes...
Then let's see...
Mama mia.
- We will have a lot of fun.
- What you can count on.
BELOVED SISTER
It is very short.
The cut does not work. I think.
If already low down.
then not so deep up.
Yes. My mother wants me to be
red. but yours is already red.
I also like red very well.
Aurora?
What is. do not
you recognize me?
Oliver.
Do not you like surprises?
Yes. but you just said
you might come by.
Well. here I am. come here.
- Is this your new style of clothes?
- Do you like it?
Yes.
- Are you introducing us?
- Clear. Natalia. that's my brother. Oliver.
- And that's my friend Nita.
- Enjoyable.
- And me first.
- Bye for now.
I have to go fast now.
- We'll talk about it later.
- Let me know which dress it will be.
- Since when are you here?
- Only a few days.
- Have you been at home with us?
- No. I stay with friends.
- You are welcome to stay with us.
- D rather not.
I think it's better that way.
How are you. sister.
You look great.
I almost did not recognize you.
- There. that's my car.
- Where is your beetle?
I sold it.
Is more something for younger.
But you are young too.
Here you go. I am very tired.
Tell me where to go.
Why are you here?
To visit friends.
And you too.
- Why do you ask?
- Why now and not sooner?
Lots to do. Aurora.
We had a lot of fun in L.A.
on my last visit.
But we'll see each other only
if I take the initiative.
You are right.
I was pretty busy in L.A.. and would
have liked to have more time.
Now I am here. and we
do not want to argue.
OK.
- Looks like always.
- Mom is not here.
Well then...
You go already?
We have just arrived.
- I'm sure she'll be the same.
- I'm late for an appointment.
- Bye for now.
- Come to dinner.
- I will. Does not matter when? Get in touch.
- Here. take the car keys.
- I'll take a rental car.
- That's OK.
- No. keep it.
- Is okay. Please take it. Oliver.
I'll take Mama's car.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Gladly.
Thank you.
I missed you very much.
I also you.
- How's your studies?
- Good.
I am trying to get a
scholarship in Colombia.
But first I have to pass the entrance
exam. otherwise I will stay here.
- Where exactly?
- In Colombia.
- In which part of Colombia?
- In Medellin.
Sounds good. Aurora.
- Honestly. I would like to travel.
- Then go through your studies.
Carlos will support me.
He wants to go there. too.
Carlos? Your friend?
Yes. but I do not like the
expression like that.
- Are you two getting along well?
- Hold still. head down.
Yes. we get along very well.
How long have you been together?
Almost 8 months already.
- 8 months?
That sounds like something serious.
What about the guy you
were with before?
Abel?
- Abel. Yes.
- Aurora!
- Was very intense.
- intensive?
- You know. typical musician.
- Aurora. are you coming down?
- Carlos is the exact opposite.
- Aurora!
I'll be right back!
OK.
Stay seated.
Hey. hey. hey!
Should I run around like this?
Quiet. I'll be right back.
I can not work.
shop and even cook.
- I really did not have time.
- Because you always have excuses.
I need your support.
You know that.
I promise you to improve.
How many times have
you promised that?
- This time it will be different.
- We will see. Now let's eat.
It's delicious. Julia.
I am lucky that
Margarita helps me.
- How long do you intend to stay?
- I do not know.
A little while.
For a while. nothing is accurate.
One week. two weeks?
Let's see.
A little while is a stretchy
term that can mean anything. Or?
You could say that...
but nothing specific.
Are you working on a new
movie or commercial?
No. Nothing like that.
I visit some friends.
and of course you two.
I longed for my sister.
I got a pirated copy of
your movie a few days ago.
- For real?
- Yes. but it did not work. Was probably broken.
How is Karen?
Karen?
Yes. Karen. your girlfriend.
Aurora told me.
Why is not she here?
I would like to meet you.
She is on the road and could
not work with her. Still wine?
- Yes.
- Me too.
Why does Oliver need your car?
He could have rented one.
- You just can not leave it. right?
- He was always selfish.
- Next time I take the bus. okay?
- That's not it. sweetheart.
You know. I'll pick you up.
It's just that your
brother is so brazen.
He appears like a ghost
and disappears again.
- See you again?
- Naturally. That's why he's here.
You will not see him again until he drives.
That's how he is.
He's suddenly there. grins.
and does what he wants.
He said he visits his
friends. then us.
Much more you.
I do not care about him.
- That's not true.
- Aurora. please. I know him.
Maybe because he
is so independent.
That bothers you because you'd rather
have everything under control.
I think he takes out too much.
Sometimes really outrageous.
Because of such sayings. he does not stay here.
I offered it to him.
- Where does he live?
- A friend leaves his apartment to him.
- Do you know him?
- no.
He is like dad.
He has friends everywhere.
- Hola.
- I have a package for Aurora Bernard.
- This is me.
- Please sign here.
Very much.
- Thank you.
- Many Thanks.
- See you soon.
- See you.
Aurora! A package for you!
Is not that a bit old fashioned?
I like it.
Did not you want to learn. Carlos?
- But.
- Do it then.
Will you give me the red pencil?
Thank you.
Leave it.
You wear a thong?
- Why not?
- Since when do you wear string tangas?
I wear them more often.
I've never seen you
But... I like it.
- I said. leave it!
- Why?
What's going on. damn it?
Do you have a problem?
If I say I do not
want. I do not want.
Yes. but you have not
wanted for two weeks.
- Do you ever think of me sometimes?
- Yes I think about you...
-... but that's not it.
- What then?
Tell me.
It's only been a few months
and it's not working anymore.
It's going well.
I do not want to beg for it.
I am so sorry to bring myself down.
Please be honest with me.
I do not know. Carlos. you're like a robot.
You always do the same thing.
Always in-out.
You could come up with
something new for a change.
Fuck yourself!
I should go out with my buddies
and look for something.
Maybe you already
have. who knows.
How is your brother?
I thought he was coming too.
I wrote to him. but
he does not answer.
- Have not heard anything for some time?
- Yes. unfortunately. Do you want one too?
With pleasure.
He looks different than
the photos you showed me.
- Yes. they were older.
- Today he looks better.
Martin looks good in
a suit. does not he?
Yes. he is very good.
- Where is Christina?
- Just stop me with Christina.
It just annoys.
She is so mediocre.
- She's your girlfriend. Nati.
- No matter. I hope she just stays home.
She drives Me Crazy.
The perfect slime.
Even if her father is influential.
So what? She is stinking bored.
He looks really good.
Not really pretty. but he has something.
Or?
Hola?
Hola. Oliver.
Good.
I am at a party.
Where are you?
Sounds good.
No idea how long that works.
Yes. I would like to. but
I can not just leave.
No. I have come first.
Oliver. certainly. if
I can do it somehow.
I'll let you know in time.
No. no. I can not
talk like that here.
OK. See you later.
Typical Natalia.
It never changes.
I am tired.
Do we want to go?
- Not!
- They are all busy with themselves.
Not here!
Not here?
- Your dress has really made me hot.
- Then take a cold shower!
What's happening?
Are you going?
Yes. I'm not so good.
Probably comes from the alcohol.
- But you said...
- I'm going.
Wait for me!
- I drive you.
- I take a taxi.
- Why a taxi? I told you...
- I'd rather take a taxi.
Damn it. Aurora. what's that?
We'll talk tomorrow. Carlos.
OK?
- Oliver.
- There you are!
Here please.
- On you two sweeties.
- To us!
- What's this?
- Do not ask. drink!
Again!
Oliver?
Hola.
Did something happen?
No. have you already slept?
No.
I just wanted to talk to you.
- You mad?
- No. why should I?
What are you doing now?
Thank you.
I want to apologize. because
of the thing recently. The...
Is everything okay.
- I was drunk. and would never have...
- No. honestly. it's all right.
Are you doing well?
I am a little tense because
of the many exams.
The exams. Naturally.
How's it going?
I'm getting distracted too
fast. that's not good.
I'm sure it will work.
You're prepared. and there's
plenty of time left. right?
Maybe. but I'm
getting bored too.
Maybe it's the daily routine.
From here to the university.
from the university back here.
That can drive you crazy.
Routine annoys me too.
No one really likes it. but it
gets worse to find it normal.
But your everyday life can
not be that bad. right?
You study what you want. you do
sports. your friend looks good.
All in all. it sounds
quite pleasant.
How do you know that
Carlos looks good?
Well... you are pretty.
or rather very pretty...
... and then I thought he had to be too.
Or not?
I do not care about externals.
that does not interest me.
But yes. he is amazing.
So I was right.
Yes. you were right.
You know...
lately nothing really works for me.
It is hopeless.
You're lucky. be content. Oliver.
You are free and have everything.
Nobody really has
everything. Aurora.
And you?
Are not you free?
No.
I do not care about freedom.
I can not handle this.
I enjoy being someone
or something.
I do not understand you.
There were times when I
would like to call you.
I wanted to know how you live your
life. but then I did not do it.
Why not?
I am your brother.
You can always call me.
even if I'm still so busy.
Yes. but I feel like
I'm bothering you.
Or that you think I'm
dying. or too attached.
- Or you are bothering.
- I would not.
I would listen.
It's getting late. Oliver.
I am tired.
Yes're right.
We should meet soon.
Only us both. for a drink.
Maybe go for a walk. so completely alone.
That's a really good idea.
I am going to bed now.
Good night.
Sleep well.
Kiss you.
- Hola.
- What are you doing here?
- Did you just take a shower?
- Yes. but come in.
- Should I come back later?
No. come on in.
Please come.
- How are you?
- Very good.
Nice.
- So that's your hiding place?
- Yes. But how do you know the address?
- You chatted it out at lunch.
- Oh yes.
- Something to drink?
- No thanks.
- If I had known. would have cleaned up here.
- Clear.
Are you working?
Yes.
Why did you come?
Just to see how and
where you live.
- I get dressed. and we have lunch. okay?
- Okay.
Make yourself at home.
I am ready!
- Let's go?
- Yes.
I quarreled with
Carlos. he's an idiot.
What was the matter?
Oh. you know. he keeps telling
me what to do or not to do.
And that annoys me.
With us. that does not work. and
I do not know how to tell him.
To be honest is
always best. right?
- Yes I think so too.
- Thank you.
I do not know. but it's not easy
to tell the whole truth to anyone.
- Someone you like. right?
- Truth can hurt or scare you.
That's true.
But that's no reason
to be sad. huh?
Do you love Carlos?
I do not know.
I mean. he's a really
nice guy. but...
I do not want to hurt him.
Would it hurt him?
I missed talking to someone.
Do you have someone?
- You mean. someone special?
- Yes exactly.
No. there is nobody.
Thank you.
- Who is the girl in the video?
- Which video?
The girl in the mud...
The video...
Have you been snooping around?
Yes. I just stumbled over it.
That's Karen.
Karen?
I'm sorry.
- I should not have looked at it.
- Is not bad. nothing happened.
What do you think
of the recordings?
Pretty violent.
Why did you do it? For a movie?
No no.
Karen likes things like that.
We make it a pleasure.
Is it your perversion?
What exactly do you call pervert?
What is strange or forbidden.
Abel also filmed me earlier.
Look.
Then you have your
perversions too?
To be honest. I
already liked it.
Are you showing me these videos?
I do not have it anymore.
He has them all.
OK.
I want to show you something.
Leave it.
You wear a thong?
- Why not?
- Since when do you wear string tangas?
I wear them more often.
I've never seen you
But I like it.
- I said. leave it!
- Why?
What's going on. damn it?
- Do you have a problem?
- When I say...
What's that about?
What do you think?
Are you taking this up now?
I keep on getting up.
How can you do that to me?
- I am your sister!
- Okay. you are my sister.
Yes.
My half sister. actually.
That's really disgusting.
Come. Aurora. you
snooped in my things.
- And my privacy?
- That is something different!
I have no camera installed with you!
This goes too far.
It's not that bad either.
- Wait. where do you want to go now?
- That was really shit. damn it.
Hey. what's wrong with you?
You are so absent.
No. everything's okay.
How about we take a break?
Away from your beloved shops?
I told you that Martin wanted
to go shopping with me.
He did it.
He bought me these great.
"silver" earrings.
That was not even silver. and I
also got a rash from the tin.
Did you expect him to buy
the shop empty for you?
I expected more.
He usually does so gallant.
- But it got worse.
- I hear...
He reproached me for
being too materialistic.
And we both know
that he is right.
Maybe you and me. but he
does not know me at all.
Besides. I'm not
just materialistic.
I like white sandy beaches. beautiful
landscapes and nature. for example.
Oh. that's why you want to make
a trip to the countryside.
He should finally see how
you can enjoy nature.
No.
I just want to get out of here.
Hey. how about?
I organize it myself.
First we go for a nice walk.
then we have a picnic.
- and invite Martin and Carlos.
- Not a good idea.
- Why?
- Carlos and I have our problems.
And that's why the variety. and the
country air will do us very well.
Bring your brother. as
an interesting addition.
Martin is a cinema connoisseur.
Then it will not be so boring.
- Okay? Yes?
- I will think about it.
Think about it?
No way.
OK.
Does your brother have a girlfriend?
Yes. Why?
- Do you like it?
- We say...
Looks like an asshole.
but yes. I like it.
He is my type.
And in the past it was yours too.
- Are you talking about Abel?
- Who else?
Abel was a dog.
But much funnier than Carlos.
He was an idiot.
Ask me how he is in bed.
Who?
Your brother.
- He's my brother!
- It may be. but he still looks...
... as if he knows where to go.
Do you think he likes it really dirty?
Can you stop it. please?
Here.
I am sorry.
I'm a back door man.
A back door man.
- Anyone else a sandwich?
- A napkin. please.
- Here please.
- Thank you.
Gladly.
- Mr. Director?
- Very attentive.
No thanks.
What kind of films do
you shoot exactly?
I do not know.
- An exact name is difficult.
- Martin is a real movie cracker.
- You would be surprised.
- That's true.
I watch at least one a day.
I have thousands on disc.
I will never manage
to look at everyone.
- Where do you get her from?
- A friend downloads it for me.
But I am very
demanding at movies.
I insist on high quality.
So only HD.
And about projector.
- Only the best.
- the finest.
- My films are not there.
- Certainly. there is everything there.
I'll go away for a moment.
Are you planning to shoot here?
No. I'm going on holiday here.
Tell me one. Oliver...
-... who else can you trust today?
- What makes you think that?
No idea. but I...
... do not get rid of the feeling
that no one dares the other today.
Even within the family.
My parents do not believe
what I tell them.
I think the topic might
be something for a movie.
Or?
People believe in you and give
you money to uncover things. Or?
- Yes.
- Things that you think are important.
But that is impossible
in this country.
No trust. Oliver.
The faith is missing.
What shoud that?
Oliver. stop it! Oliver!
Oliver. let me go!
And what about the camera?
You like that!
Take me Home.
- What shoud that?
- Come here!
Why are you doing this?
That hurts!
Listen to me!
Please stop! Mummy!
Mummy!
Mom. let me out of here!
Open up!
Open the door!
Mummy!
Let me out!
Mummy...
Finally say something.
You are not in court here.
How reassuring.
But if you want we can talk
about what has happened.
I do not want to talk about it.
I want to go home.
I'm good.
What does "good" mean for you?
Be satisfied with yourself.
Be happy.
Are you happy?
I'm only doing this for my mother.
I am old enough.
Do you have a Friend?
- no.
- Are you dating someone?
Not any longer longer.
What's his name?
- Carlos.
And what do you think...
how Carlos feels at that moment?
I'm not interested.
Why?
Did not you love him?
Or at least liked it?
What kind of question is that?
How much did you like him?
That's enough.
And how much compared
to her brother?
Have you ever heard?
She slept with her own brother.
Your own brother.
- She sleeps with everyone.
- She's perverted.
- Like an animal.
- Animal and perverted.
- How sick.
- Just disgusting. this idea.
I agree.
You said it.
Simply disgusting.
Aurora?
What do you want?
You are intelligent. do
not behave like an idiot.
- I want to go to my sister.
- You are sick.
- You can not stop me. Julia.
- And if that's the last thing I do.
- Stay away from her.
- You do not understand what this is about.
You're a son of a bitch!
Leave Aurora alone.
Julia. please.
Better leave the city. you hear?
Leave the country.
I'll kill you if
I see you again.
You know. I'm serious.
I do not hesitate.
This is not an empty threat!
Son of a bitch.
Are you hungry?
No.
- Are you going to eat up here again today?
- Yes.
But you could also eat
down with me together.
- Did Oliver call?
- Please what?
Did Oliver call?
- What's the point. damn it?
- I do not want you to talk to him.
- The bastard. how could he?
- But nothing happened.
Carlos disagrees.
- Carlos is lying.
- Maybe. but not Oliver.
He just told me everything.
Love...
Oliver just played with you.
- The whole thing did not mean anything to him.
- Maybe I'll go to L.A. with him.
You will not go with anyone. nowhere.
You are sick. Aurora.
And you have to be in therapy.
It was just sex. mom.
Try it too.
Are you crazy?
So you admit it?
I am an adult!
You can not lock me up forever!
You are still a child!
How was he when
you were a child?
- Rebellious. father said.
- Okay I see.
And how would you describe
him. in your own words?
Mysterious. Yes...
He was mysterious.
- And was the relationship with his father good?
- No. they did not get along.
- And with your mother Julia?
- Even worse.
She was not his mother.
so that was normal.
- Do you think...? Find?
- Yes I think so.
And...
Does she have the...
... somehow worried. or
was it okay with you?
I do not know.
Think about it.
Maybe you like it...
... that he could not
handle her parents?
Yes... he was different.
It was an unpleasant
situation for everyone.
He fell out of the frame.
That can be attractive and captivating.
- What was so different?
- He was violent and destructive.
He took Father's car and
disappeared for days.
That's out of line for you?
Yes. he dared to do things
that I would not even say.
As...
... would you describe him today?
Still mysterious?
- I do not know.
- Try it. With just a word.
Dark.
He is a dark person now.
As a kid I often watched him.
He was so different from everyone else.
As if he had no feelings.
I do not know how he endured all
these quarrels with my dad.
Then he went away?
Felt unwell.
- How did you feel?
- Facilitated.
From then on everything went
as my parents had planned.
What do you think. why does your
brother like to break all the rules?
To the satisfaction.
Is that what he
wanted you to do?
Sorry?
Just breaking the rules?
Do not believe.
Why should it be different?
What happens when he leaves?
Maybe he is already gone.
I dont know.
How are you feeling today?
Good.
Does this thing have
to be on all the time?
- Give it to me!
- Stop it!
Give it to me!
It is enough!
Aurora. what are you doing?
Aurora! Where do you want to go?
Oliver!
Aurora.
I tried to call.
- Where have you been?
- I was forbidden to meet you.
- You tried?
- Yes. I was in the club. but you were not there.
Oh yes?
You've let me down.
No. you were never alone.
Aurora.
- What happened?
- Nothing. I fell.
I'm sorry. what you had to
go through because of me.
- I could not do anything.
- It was so terrible.
Natalia?
You mean bitch.
I a bitch?
I?
Are you completely crazy now?
- hooker!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Which of us fucked his brother?
- I'll kill you. whore!
Stop!
- Go better now.
- You are crazy.
Fuck off! Get out!
And you are a cretin!
- You're sick!
- How can you be so disgusting?
You are scum!
And mean!
Fuck you. you bitch!
I do not believe it.
- That was not planned.
- What do you mean by that?
That with her or me?
- What exactly should not have happened?
- This one. You should not have come.
Please tell me the truth:
How long have you been kidding me?
- I never fooled you. Honestly.
- Oh yes? And then what the shit?
- It should not have happened.
- You repeat yourself. Oliver! It happened!
- There was an error! I can explain it!
- What do you want to explain?
That you climb over my best friend
while I was locked up at home?
No.
Do you know what respect is?
Do you have respect for something?
- Calm down. then we talk.
- Yes. Then you will notice something intelligent.
You're a fucker and a bastard.
A shame. Oliver.
You have lost something very
important in your life.
You are really perverted.
Humiliation is normal for you.
That's why your life
is so dark and empty.
Get out of my life.
- Oliver Bernard?
- Yes I am.
Here is an envelope for you.
Please sign here.
OK.
- Thank you. That's it.
- Bye for now.
What the hell is that?
I swear it looks like a ritual
punishment for adultery.
That's it.
Sit back. relax. and just
enjoy the performance.
Now. hopefully. you
know who you belong to.
At that time the man
was still a man.